<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Penta Global</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Penta Global</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Penta (PNT) Announcement on the First Stage of the Buyback Program</title>
      <link>/blog/penta-buyback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/penta-buyback/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Penta community members:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On July 16, 2018, The Penta Global Foundation initiated the first stage of a buyback program on secondary markets, amounting to a total buyback of 200 million PNT. As of 10:46am (Singapore Time) on July 23, 2018, Penta has fully completed the Stage 1 buyback.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penta Network Governance</title>
      <link>/blog/penta-network-governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/penta-network-governance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Overview&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary goals of the Penta public blockchain are: decentralization, fairness and trust. In order to meet these, besides Penta, any public blockchain project needs to have a clear governance structure to avoid destructive actions or misaligned intentions by the core developers, or the block producers.   Penta aims for a governance process that is both transparent and robust to corruption.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LFE and Penta Partnership Announcement</title>
      <link>/blog/lfe-penta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/lfe-penta/</guid>
      <description>Announcing the biggest blockchain project in football. The London Football Exchange is joining forces with Penta, a next generation public blockchain, to build the first decentralized application for a fan-driven football community. LFE and Penta will offer fans worldwide the chance to experience football in a new and exciting way: receive access to exclusive event tickets, private tours of football clubs and stadiums, opportunities to meet with your favourite football stars and coaches, special merchandise offers, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penta (PNT) Trading on HADAX Postponed, to Open at 15:00, June 22</title>
      <link>/blog/trading-on-hadax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:03:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/trading-on-hadax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to HADAX system issues, Penta (PNT) trading which was originally scheduled to open 15:00, June 20(GMT+8) will be postponed to open at 15:00, June 22 (GMT+8).  Withdrawals will be available from 14:30 June 23, 2018 (GMT+8). Sorry for the inconvenience caused.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penta (PNT) official announcement to the community</title>
      <link>/blog/linked-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/linked-post/</guid>
      <description>Penta (PNT) official announcement to the community The Penta Global Foundation believes that recent market pressures have driven the price of PNT far below its true value. In response, the Penta Global Foundation has decided to initiate a buyback program on secondary markets.The total buyback will be 10% of the current circulating supply, amounting to 1.8 billion PNT. As of July 16, 2018, Penta officially started the first stage of the buyback process with a total amount of 200 million PNT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is for lovers</title>
      <link>/blog/go-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/go-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo uses the excellent &lt;a href=&#34;http://golang.org/&amp;gt;&#34;&gt;go&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://golang.org/pkg/html/template/&amp;gt;&#34;&gt;html/template&lt;/a&gt; library for
its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very
small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of
logic to be able to create a good static website.   If you have used other
template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of
similarities in go templates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>